我需要你给我签字
I need you to sign something.
什么
What you got?
好的
Okay.
乔丹  我一周前就该签字的
Jordan, I was supposed to sign this a week ago.
怎么现在才给我
How come I'm just now getting it?
我忘了
I forgot.
而且你全得了C
And it's all C's.
你很聪明的  乔丹
You're a smarter kid than this, Jordan.
这看上去根本不像你的成绩单
This doesn't even look like your report card.
你签不签
Are you gonna sign it, or what?
我会签  但是你要明白  乔丹
I'm signing. But understand, Jordan.
虽然你这几周过得很不顺
It's been a rough couple of weeks,
但这都不是理由
but there's no excuse for this.
这都不...
There's no--
听着
Listen.
我们待会再聊这件事  好吗
We will talk about that later. Okay?
好吗
All right?
安东尼奥有新动向吗
Anything new with Antonio?
没有  但我还是想盯着他
No, but I still want to keep an eye on him.
拿到了马歇尔·卡特住处的搜查令
Got a search warrant for the residence of Marshall Carter.
他是暗夜领主帮的老大
He's the head of the Night Lords.
他有非法持械和斗殴罪的前科
He's got priors for possession, aggravated battery.
他们在黑格维施一幢房子外交易
They deal out of a house in Hegewisch.
在郊区
The boonies.
是的  我的线人确认
Yeah. My C.I. confirmed
会在这里进行每月例行分销
the monthly shipments here ready for distribution.
是这样的  餐厅中
Now, here's the thing. There's an estimated
估计有市值近两百万的
street value of at least two mil worth of meth and cocaine
冰毒和可卡因
in the dining room.
-有多少人  -至少六人
- How many men? - Uh, at least six.
地址是橡树街238号
The address is 238 Five Oaks Road.
出发吧
Let's hit it.
芝加哥警署  转过去
Chicago PD! Turn around.
-转过去  -趴下
- Turn around. - Get down.
-两腿分开  -安全
- Spread your legs. - Clear.
-还有人  -有人跑了
- Wider. - Hey, we got a runner.
面对墙  蹲着别动
Stay against the wall. Stay on the ground.
你想去哪儿呢  小子
The hell you thought you was going, boy?
瞧瞧这是谁
Look who it is.
-马歇尔·卡特先生  -我们抓住他了
- Mr. Marshall Carter. - We got him.
所有人都在这里
That's all of them.
起来
Sit back. Get up.
-你听到了吗  -嗯
- You hear that? - Yeah.
小家伙  小家伙
Little guy, little guy.
小家伙  你要去哪
Little guy. Hey, where you going?
你要去哪  过来  过来
Where you going? Come here, come here.
没事了  没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
I got you. I got you.
里面还有人吗  警长
Anybody else in there, Sarge?
两个孩子
Two kids.
都死了
Both dead.
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第五集
查不到那孩子的身份  和那两个孩子一样
So, the kid's a ghost. Same with the other two kids.
没有失踪报告
No one's reported them missing.
我查了本地和全国范围内的
I ran facial recognition locally,
面部识别系统  还和联调局进行比对
nationally, and double checked with the FBI.
什么结果都没有
I got nothing.
-有名字吗  -没有
- They got a name? - No.
-那孩子不会说英文  -我找了几名翻译
- The kid doesn't speak English. - I called a few translators.
也许能有发现
Maybe we'll get lucky.
现在的情况是三名孩子遭到囚禁
Look, the fact is three kids were held captive.
两名死亡  必须有人为此付出代价
Two of them are dead. Someone's gonna pay for this.
-干得不错  -嗯
- Good work. - Yeah.
-谢了  -没事
- Thanks. - Yeah.
我知道你听不懂我说话
I know you don't understand me.
但你现在安全了
But you are in a safe place.
越南
Vietnam.
你来自越南
You're from Vietnam?
谢谢你
Thank you.
跟我们说说那小棚子里孩子的事
Tell us about the kids in the shelter.
什么孩子
What kids?
我们在你的避雨棚里发现了一名黑人儿童
A black kid, a white kid, and an Asian kid
一名白人儿童和一名亚裔儿童
were found in your storm shelter.
我不知道什么孩子的事
I don't know nothing about no kids.
那个看起来就不正常的棚子不是我的
And that creepy-looking shelter ain't mine.
是后面那幢楼的
It belongs to the house in back.
最好如此
You better hope so.
-你的邻居是谁  -我怎么知道
- Who's your neighbor? - Hell if I know.
回答错误  马歇尔
That's the wrong answer, Marshall.
-什么  -我们抓到你
- Excuse me? - We got you on
在分销毒品
distribution, methamphetamine production,
如果我们查不出什么  还要加上两起命案
and until we learn otherwise, double homicide.
对了  我忘记提了
Oh, yeah. I forget to mention
其中两个孩子死了
two of the kids are dead?
这两个孩子的死因都是接触四氯化碳
C.O.D. For both children was carbon tetrachloride exposure.
那是一种用来提取冰毒的溶剂
It's a solvent used to extract meth.
他们是吸入了气体
So they inhaled fumes?
不  他们的腹内有掺毒的水
No, there was toxic water in their stomach contents.
我猜是毒贩将废弃用水
My guess is the drug dealers dumped the waste products
倒在院子里  渗进了地下水
into the yard and it seeped into the ground water.
好吧  然后孩子们渴了
Okay, so, the kids got thirsty,
喝了地上的水  然后痛苦地死了
drank the puddle of water, they got sick, and died.
感觉是这样
Sounds about right.
-好  谢谢  -不客气
- Okay, thanks. - You're welcome.
我们核查了一下
Hey. So, we did some checking.
你说得没错
Turns out you're right.
那个棚子是你邻居的
Storm shelter belongs to your neighbor.
我说什么来着  我承认贩毒
What'd I say? I admit to the dope,
但我跟孩子没关系
but I ain't copping to them kids.
我从来没去过那个棚子
I've never been near that shelter.
你们可以搞些什么犯罪现场调查来证明
You can do some CSI crap to prove it.
你想知道犯罪现场调查证明了什么吗
You wanna know what that CSI crap proves?
你们倒进地里的制毒废料
The meth waste you dumped in the yard
流进了防护棚
seeped into the shelter.
那些孩子们喝了以后死了
The kids drank it and died.
猜猜这叫什么
Wanna guess what that's called?
这叫刑事疏忽杀人
It's called criminally negligent homicide.
我什么都交代
I'll tell you everything I know.
我和绑架小孩的疯子
I got no allegiance to some freak
可没有任何关系
who's snatching up little kids.
那就交代吧
So start talking.
我见过他两次  他两次都和小孩一起
I saw him two times. Both times, he was with kids.
第一次是两个女孩  第二次是三个男孩
First time was two girls. Second time was three boys.
他长什么样
What did he look like?
高大的白人  挺老了  大概有50岁
Tall white dude. Old, like, 50.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
他叫关娃  他来自萨帕
His name is Quan Vo. He's from Sapa,
翻译     小酸奶   风城章鱼X
是北越南的一个小山村
a mountain village in northern Vietnam.
-他什么时候来到芝加哥的  -六周前
- When did he get to Chicago? - Six weeks ago.
他本来住在孤儿院  然后被送往美国
He was living at an orphanage, and then he was sent to America
翻译     小萝莉   H小欠   pang   圈圈
前往新的寄养家庭
to bless a new family.
他知道新的寄养家庭叫什么名字吗
Okay, uh, the new family. Does he know their name?
校对     圈圈
他只知道一个名字  史密斯
The only name he knows is "Smith."
他本来和他们住在一起  直到两天前
He was living with them up until two days ago.
时间轴     西查   chance-coco
然后发生了什么
All right, what happened after that?
那对史密斯夫妇将他给了另一对夫妻
That couple, the Smiths, gave him to another couple,
那对夫妻将他给了另一个人
then that couple gave him to another man
后期     8T
然后他们把他关了起来
who then locked him up in some sort of cellar.
他能描述那些人的长相吗
Can he describe any of these people?
总监     圈圈
他们都是白人
They were all white.
他们的地址呢  他知道他们住在哪里吗
And, uh, their address. Does he know where they lived?
不知道  但是那是一幢黄褐色的房子
No, but it was a tan house.
在火车边
Near a train.
在火车附近
Near a train?
画着猫
Has a picture of cats.
还有种椰子奶油粉的味道
And it smelled like Bánh Socola Bột Nếp.
什么  什么东西
What is that...  What?
你能再说一遍吗
Can you say that again?
-椰子奶油粉  -椰子...
- Bánh Socola Bột Nếp. - Banh Socola...
那是个什么东西
And that...What is that?
吃的  一道越南菜
Food. A Vietnamese dish.
我以前也没吃过
I've never had it before.
好吧  我联系附近的饭店
Okay, I'm gonna call a restaurant and see
看能不能点一份
if I can get that order.
好的
Copy that.
代我们说声谢谢
Tell him, "Thank you."
他想告诉你他刚被锁进去的时候
He wants you to know the other two kids were alive
另外两个孩子还活着
when he was first locked up.
他告诉他们不要喝那里的水
He told them not to drink the water,
但他们没听
but they didn't listen.
他想救他们
He tried to save them.
普拉特说有人从皇家暹罗饭店点了道菜
Platt said someone ordered from Royal Siam?
-我的  -闻起来好香
- Right here. - Smells delicious.
有避雨棚的那栋房子
Okay, the house with the storm shelter's
注册在开曼群岛一家公司名下
registered to an LLC in Grand Cayman.
他们在芝加哥大约有两百套房产
They have about 200 units here in Chicago.
但这一套因为地基问题被标红了
This one was red-tagged for foundation problems.
应该没人住的
It should be empty.
所以这个嫌疑人是擅自住进去的
So our suspect was squatting.
看来是这样
Sounds like it.
这么说我们没查到名字和号码
So we got no name, no number,
什么都没有
no nothing.
没法相信  是巧克力
Huh. Unbelievable, it's chocolate.
就是巧克力
It's chocolate.
关说他住的房子有股这种味道
Quan said the house he lived in smelled like this.
很好
Sweet.
所以肯定在巧克力工厂附近
So, must be around one of the chocolate factories.
有结果吗
What've we got?
他们已经找了五家
Well, they've been to five houses
名字叫史密斯的住户了
owned by people named Smith.
还是没有匹配的  所以我也不知道
Still no hits, so I don't know.
看来只能继续找下去了
I guess just keep knocking.
等等  等一下
Wait, wait, wait a second.
关说房子外面画着什么来着
Quan said there was a picture of what outside the house?
猫
Cats.
很好
Okay.
不好意思  你们有什么事吗
Excuse me. Can I help you?
有  我们是阿特沃特警官和鲁塞克警官
Yeah. Officer Atwater. This is officer Ruzek.
芝加哥警署的  我们希望你
Chicago PD. We were hoping that
能帮我们确定下这个男孩的身份
you could help us identify this little boy.
这是我儿子关  我领养的
That's my son, Quan. He's adopted.
怎么回事
What's this about?
你们好  怎么了
Hi. What's going on?
是警察  他们问关的事
It's the police. They're asking about Quan.
什么  关被绑架了
What...Quan was kidnapped?
我们也在调查这件事
That's what we're trying to figure out.
好吧  我之前出差去了
Okay. I was away on a business trip.
关应该在上学的
He...Quan's supposed to be in school.
好吧  但他没有
Right, but he's not.
你最后一次看到他是什么时候
When was the last time you saw him?
告诉他啊
Well, just tell him.
你最后一次看到关是什么时候
When was the last time you saw Quan?
就是今早  对吧
It was this morning, right?
两天前
Two days ago.
Two days ago?
怎么可能
How's that possible?
你根本不知道这孩子有多难管
You know how difficult he was.
那么多问题  我根本应付不来
All the problems that I was having.
别  别  别说了
Don't, don't, don't. Stop.
告诉我你做了什么
Just tell me what you did.
我  找到了这么一个网站
I...I found a web site,
有一对非常有爱的夫妻
and there was this really lovely couple.
你把我们儿子送人了
You gave our son away?
你怎么能这么做  怎么忍心
How could you do that? How?
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
-怎么能  -和我去厨房
- How? - Walk to the kitchen with me.
我们会查清楚的
We're gonna figure this out.
从寄养到领养
你们必须要明白  关有问题
You have to understand that Quan has issues.
他老是偷钱  偷吃的
He was always stealing money, food...
我受不了了
It was too much.
但是跨国领养
But with foreign adoptions,
根本不知道去哪里求助
there's nowhere you can turn for help.
所以我就在网上找互助小组
So I started looking for a support group online.
然后我就找到了这个真心承诺网
And that's when I found this Real Promises web site.
所以  你就这么把他送人了
So... You just gave him away?
孤儿院对我们隐瞒了他的情况
The orphanage lied to us about him.
我们要的是五岁以下的孩子
We asked for a boy under five,
结果他们把关送来了
and instead they sent Quan.
托德根本不知道这有多难
Todd had no idea how bad it was.
他总是在忙工作
He was always working.
只有我一个人在家应付这么多事
I was the one who was home alone dealing with all of this.
我害怕了  我只是
And I was scared. I was...
我害怕他会伤害我家的双胞胎姐妹
I was scared that he was gonna hurt our twin girls.
她们还太小  才刚满四岁
They're...they're young. They just turned four.
你从来没有因为这孩子不好管教
And you never told your wife to get rid of him
就叫你妻子把他送走
because he was difficult?
-没有  -从来没有吗
- No. - Never?
绝对没有
Absolutely not.
你能想到她会做这种事情吗
Did you ever think she would do something like this?
想不到
Never.
我不在乎我妻子说了什么做了什么
I don't care what my wife said or what she did.
我爱我儿子
I love my son.
我愿意做任何事情  只求他回来
I would do anything to get him back.
没那么简单
It's not that simple.
为什么
Why not?
你妻子把一个小男孩送给了两名陌生人
Your wife gave away a little boy to two strangers,
然后这两个人又把孩子送给了一个大高个
who then gave him away to some tall guy
然后孩子被他锁在避雨棚里
who locked him in a storm shelter.
所以才不简单
That's why not.
所以你上了这个真心承诺网
So you went to this Real Promises web site,
发了一条信息  然后说
you sent a message that said,
"我家孩子需要新的家庭"
"We have a child that needs a new home."
第二天你就收到了来自约翰和
The next day you get a response from a John
佩妮·马斯登夫妇的回复  对吧
and a Penny Marsden, right?
是  他们希望马上见面
Yeah, they wanted to meet right away.
你具体什么时候和马斯登夫妇见面的
When exactly did you meet the Marsdens?
那天下午四点
That afternoon at 4:00.
关放学回家之后
When Quan got home from school.
好的  马斯登夫妇是什么样子
Right, um... What'd the Marsdens look like?
丈夫个子不高  然后
The husband was short, and, um...
妻子的相貌很普通
The wife was just average-looking.
两个人大概都四十岁上下的样子
Uh, they were probably both about 40.
好的  电话号码呢
Okay. Um...Telephone number?
地址
Address?
都没有
No.
你一定觉得我很恶劣
You think I'm awful. I know.
我跟你说实话
To be honest with you,
我觉得情况多么恶劣并不是重点
I don't think it matters how bad the situation is.
最恶劣的是你居然把孩子送人  史密斯夫人
I think it's very extreme to give a kid away, Mrs. Smith.
凯特·史密斯的行为还有个专有名词
So, what Kate Smith did has a name.
叫做"重新安置"
It's called "Re-homing."
我看该叫"不可饶恕"
It's called "Unforgivable."
的确  但在伊利诺伊州是合法的
Uh, yeah, but it's legal in the state of Illinois.
跨国领养的父母可以在法官批准下
Parents can transfer the care of foreign adoptees
领养法无法保护"重新安置"儿童的权益
把被领养人转交给其他人抚养
to someone else with a power of attorney.
几年前在聊天室就开始这样了
It started a few years back in chat rooms.
凯特·史密斯用的那个网站查得怎么样了
What about the web site Kate Smith used?
是个骗子网站
It's a sham.
运营半年了
It's been around for six months.
IP地址是通过暗网的
The IP address is routed through the dark net.
来源在冰岛
And the origin is listed as Iceland.
马斯登夫妇根本不存在
This Marsden couple does not exist.
芝加哥地区没有约翰或者佩妮·马斯登的
There's not a record of a John or Penny Marsden
任何记录
in the Chicago land area.
真人令人震惊啊  人贩子用的是化名
Shocker. A child trafficker is using fake names.
我们得去搭个线
So we need to make contact.
找到领养关的马斯登夫妇
Find this Marsden couple and the mystery man
-和神秘人  -警长
- they gave Quan to. - Yo, Sarge,
让我和金试试看
let me and Kim have a shot at him.
我们可以假扮一对送养孩子的夫妇
We can pose as a couple wanting to give a kid away.
给网站发一条信息
Send a message out there to the web site.
打赌可以引蛇出洞
I bet we can draw them in.
好主意
All right, good.
我不希望这些"重新安置"的混蛋
Hey, I don't want these re-homing punks
发现我们盯上他们了  明白吗
thinking we're on to them, you understand?
-明白  -好的
- Copy that. - Yeah.
发现一辆浅色SUV里的
Got a male driver and a female passenger
男性司机和女性乘客  伊利诺伊牌照
in a light-colored SUV. Illinois tags,
33JP60
33 John Paul 60.
收到
Copy that.
车辆注册在约翰· 金斯利名下
Vehicle is registered to John Kingsley.
注册地址在塔湖公寓
Address listed is the Tower Lake apartments,
但那里两年前就拆了
but those were torn down two years ago.
我们也有考虑国外领养
We thought about foreign adoption, too.
但开销太大
But, you know, it all takes money.
-耗时  -我不想等了
- And time. - I'm tired of waiting.
我现在就想当母亲
I wanna be a mother now.
我看到你们女儿的消息后
And when I read about your little girl,
我觉得这是上天注定的事
I knew that this was meant to be.
佩妮说她找到了自己的小天使
Yeah, Penny said she found her angel.
没错  我的心都融化了
It's true. My heart melted.
你们为什么要送养她
So, um, why do you want to give her up?
相信我  我们并不想的
Uh, trust me, we--we don't.
但是工作啊
But, you know with work
-旅行啊  对吧  -对的
- and travel, right? - Yeah.
我们经常旅行  我只是不想...
We travel so much, I just don't--
我觉得我们没法给娜迦
I don't think we really can give Naja
-需要的陪伴  -好吧
- the time she deserves. - Yeah.
我理解
I understand.
你们看上去都是很好的人
Look, you all seem like really nice people.
但我们想确定
But we just wanna make sure
不会有后续的麻烦
that we don't get into trouble later.
你们知道是谁创立真心承诺网的吗
Do you know who started the Real Promises web site?
不知道  但是合法的
No, but it's legal.
我知道一对曾用过这个网站的夫妇
Uh, I know of a couple that used it before.
他们领养了一个俄罗斯的可爱男孩
They adopted just a terrific boy from Russia.
那太好了
Oh, that's so great.
我们想和他们聊聊
We would love to talk to them.
天呐  他们是我们以前邻居的朋友
Oh, gosh, they were friends of our old neighbors.
我不记得他们的名字了
I don't remember their names.
我们可以理解
Yeah, we understand It happens.
我们可以见见娜迦吗
So, um, can we meet Naja?
乔丹来电
抱歉  当然可以了
Sorry about that. Of course you can.
我们可以看看你们的房子吗
But, uh, how about we check out the house?
很快的  我们知道你们有照片
Just real quick. We know that you have pictures.
我们有两英亩的地  对很多人而言
We are on two acres. And it's a little rural
有些田园风  但我们很喜欢
for a lot of folks, but we just love it.
很美
It's beautiful.
我们现在就去看看吧
Well, hey, let's check this out now.
-我很激动  -现在吗
- I mean, I'm excited. - Right now?
-是啊  -我们没有时间
- Yeah. - We don't have time
开个来回  但是...
to drive there and back. But, um, it is--
-那是很棒的房子  -是啊
- It's a very nice house. - Yeah, it is.
但我们得看看才放心
But we're gonna need to check it out,
也许也要和相关的人聊一聊
and maybe talk to a few references, too.
我觉得你们还没有准备好
You know, I don't think you're ready to do this.
-我们走吧  约翰  -感谢
- We should leave, John. - Thank you.
-见到你们很高兴  -是啊
- It was nice to meet you. - Yeah.
很荣幸
Pleasure.
朝你们那边过去了
They're headed out to you.
好的
All right.
看起来不像是罗西克莱尔的农场
Doesn't look like a farm in Rosiclare.
是啊  我也没看到轮胎秋千
Yeah, I don't see that tire swing, either.
看到了吗
See that?
看上去里面不止两个人
Looks like there might be more than two people in there.
还有一辆车
We got another car.
我是D5021  中心
5021 David. Hey, uh, squad,
能帮我查一辆伊利诺伊州的车吗
can you run a Illinois passenger,
棕色路虎揽胜
brown in color, Range Rover,
牌照710Z5N
710 Zebra 5 Nora?
收到  你的位置
10-4. Where can I hold you down?
保密南路90号
90 South Confidential.
收到
Copy that.
我是B5021  有枪击事件  派后援来
5021 Baker. Shots fired, send backup.
注意  现场有便衣警察
Be advised, plain clothes officers responding.
收到
Copy that.
芝加哥警署  放下枪
Chicago PD, drop the gun.
除非他告诉我对关做了什么
Not until he tells me what he did to Quan.
-警官  救命  -托德  别这样
- Officer, please. - Todd, don't do this, man.
-出去  不然我杀了他  -别 只...
- Get out, or I'll kill him. - No, no, just--
闭嘴  女士  快闭嘴  好吗
Shut up! Lady, just shut up, okay?
-退后  -出去  不然他死定了
- Step back. - Get out or he's dead.
告诉他们  告诉他们
You tell them. You tell them
你对我儿子做了什么
what you did to my son.
从后门进去
Go to the back.
托德  我知道你很生气  但别做
Todd, I know you're upset, but don't do something
-你会后悔的事  -不值得
- you're gonna regret here. - It's not worth it.
-让我们来处理  -你还有其他孩子
- Just let us handle this. - You got other kids.
他们不想长大的时候  爸爸在监狱
They don't wanna grow up with a dad in prison.
-放下枪  -拜托
- Put the gun down. - Please.
放下枪  别逼我们
Put the gun down. Don't make us do it.
他们抢走了我的孩子
They took my boy.
他们是罪犯  他们手上有我的孩子
No, they're the criminals. They've got my kid.
-我们得谈谈  -等等  你是那个母亲
- We need to talk. - Wait, you're the mother?
不  我是警察
No, I'm the police.
-我只是想让儿子回来  -冷静
- I just want my son. - Calm down.
冷静  结束了
Calm down. It's over.
哪一个更差劲  领养孩子的
What's worse, people taking the kids,
还是一开始送养孩子的
or the ones giving them away in the first place?
领养的  毫无疑问
People taking them, no doubt.
我刚收到乔丹的短信
I just got a text from Jordan.
-我得走了  -怎么了
- I should go. - What is it?
不知道  和凡妮莎的
I don't know. Some kind of problem
问题  没事的
with Vinessa. It's okay.
-什么事  -他没说
- What kind of problem? - He didn't say.
-我必须过去  -我跟你一起去
- I just gotta go. - Well, I'm coming with you.
出什么事了
Hey, hey, what's going on?
-有人攻击了她  -什么
- Some guys attacked her. - What?
我到家就看到她这样了
I came home and I found her like this.
怎么了  凡妮莎
Huh? Hey, hey, Vinessa.
你还好吗  还好吗  宝贝丫头
Are you okay? You okay, baby girl?
和我说说  怎么了
Talk to me, huh? What happened?
怎么了
What happened?
他们把我拖到巷子里
They pulled me into an alley.
说会强奸我
Said they were gonna rape me
因为"你哥哥是告密的人"
'cause "Your brother's a snitch."
什么  然后发生了什么
What? Okay, what happened after that?
把情况原原本本地告诉我  凡妮莎
Tell me exactly what happened, Vinessa.
然后...
Then...
一辆面包车开进了巷子  他们  他们就跑了
A truck came down the alley, so they, um, they ran away.
凡妮莎
Uh, Vinessa...
那些人  他们有没有伤害你
These guys, did they hurt you in any way?
-没有  -他们是谁
- No. - Who were they?
你记得他们是谁吗
Huh? You remember who they were?
我  我不知道  就是
I--I don't know. Just, um,
附近的孩子
some kids from the neighborhood.
别再撒谎了  凡妮莎  告诉我们是谁
Stop lying, Vinessa. Just tell us who the guys are.
-乔丹  -她认识...
- Jordan-- - She knows ev--
乔丹  这个事情交给我  好吗
Jordan, I'm gonna take care of this, okay?
你上楼去  冷静一下
Just go upstairs and calm down.
有我在
I got it.
别难过  我们会搞清楚这事的
I'm so sorry. We gonna figure this out.
我想凡妮莎可能需要喝杯热巧克力
Figured Vinessa could use some hot chocolate.
那些孩子到底是怎么知道乔丹的事的
How the hell did those kids find out about Jordan?
他也就选了张照片
All he did was pick a photo
-在陪审团面前做了个证  -我不知道
- and testify in front of a grand jury. - I don't know.
怎么会这样呢  金
How did that happen, Kim? Huh?
我他妈完全想不通
I mean, it doesn't make no damn sense to me.
我真的不懂  现在我必须得处理好
I just don't get it. And now I gotta deal with it.
-这是什么意思  -我不知道
- What does that mean? - I don't know.
凯文
Kevin.
我有个阿姨在德州  她说我应该
I got a auntie in Texas who said I should probably
把孩子们送去跟她住
send the kids down there to live with her.
-你觉得呢  -我觉得这些孩子需要我
- What do you think? - I think those kids need me.
我就是这么想的
That's what I think.
更重要的是  我需要他们
More than anything, I need them.
所以我到底该怎么办
So what the hell am I supposed to do?
-把他们送走吗  -不  想都别想
- Re-home them? - No, don't even go there.
凯文  这个完全不一样
Kevin, it's completely different.
不一样  怎么不一样
How? How's it different?
-就  就是不一样  -在我看来
- It--It's just different. - It doesn't seem
没什么不一样  金  现在没有不一样
different to me right now, Kim. Not right now.
你们搞错了
You've got this all wrong.
我们去接那孩子是为了救他
We picked up that boy to rescue him.
救他
Oh, rescue him.
我们在为移民海关总署的卧底人员工作
We're working for an undercover ICE agent.
克莱德·哈里斯
Clyde Harris.
他在调查人口贩卖
He's investigating human trafficking,
特别是丢弃领养儿童的父母
especially parents giving away adopted children.
好吧  所以  你去接关
Okay, so, you picked up Quan,
把他交给移民总署的人  克莱德·哈里斯
and you gave him to this ICE agent, Clyde Harris.
-对  -但他最后去了避雨棚
- Right. - But he ended up in a storm shelter.
跟他一起的另外两个孩子都死了
With two other kids who are both dead.
我们两个月前在一个"生存权"集会活动上
We met Clyde Harris a couple of months ago
认识了克莱德·哈里斯
at a Right to Life rally downtown.
我们聊了聊  他说
We got to talking, and he said,
"你想救救孩子  顺便还能赚点小钱吗"
"Do you wanna save kids and maybe make a little extra cash?"
我们说  "想"
And we said, "Yes."
想救孩子还是想赚钱
Save kids, or make extra cash?
当然是救孩子
Save kids, of course.
好吧  我不骗你
Okay, all right. I won't lie.
能赚钱也挺好
The extra money helps.
我是残疾人  我妻子是房地产经纪人
I'm on disability, and my wife's a realtor.
你也知道  生意不太好
And, you know, business isn't great.
他给你们多少
How much was he giving you?
-一个孩子五百元  -一个孩子五百元
- $500 a kid. - $500 a kid?
这时薪也太他妈高了
That's a hell of a payday for a few hours of work.
我们没有理由怀疑克莱德
We had no reason to doubt Clyde.
从来没有
Ever.
好吧  解释一下这是怎么操作的
Okay, explain to me how this works.
哈里斯需要你们帮忙时
When agent Harris needs your help,
-怎么联系你们  -他打我手机
- how does he contact you? - He calls my cell phone.
每次的电话号码都不一样
And it's always from a different number.
他告诉我们去见谁  什么时候  在哪里
He tells us who we're supposed to meet, when, and where.
你们装作不孕症夫妇
You pretend to be an infertile couple
想收养孩子  马斯登夫妇
who wants to adopt. The Marsdens.
别人会把他们的孩子给我们  什么都不问
People give us their kids. No questions asked.
大部分时间都不问
I mean, most of the time, anyway.
然后呢  你们带孩子去哪里
And then what? Where do you take the kids?
我们  我们在I94号附近的
We--we meet agent Harris out
货车停车场见哈里斯
at a truck stop near I-94.
好  我们给哈里斯打个电话试试
Okay. Let's try and call agent Harris.
也许我们可以在停车场见见他
Maybe we can meet him at that truck stop.
-密码是多少  -9934
- What's your pass code? - 9934.
9934.
-哪个号码是哈里斯的  -第二个
- Which number is for agent Harris? - It's the second one,
但经常会变
but it changes all the time.
他这个工作必须用一次性手机
He has to use burner phones for his job, you know?
-好  -你今天下午给哈里斯打过电话吗
- Right. - You called Clyde this afternoon?
就跟他说我们没有接到孩子
Just to tell him that we didn't pick up the child.
打不通
It's disconnected.
他是怎么找到房车的
So how'd he find that trailer?
佩妮·马斯登签完委托书
Penny Marsden left behind a Bright Morning Realty pen
留下了一支明曦地产的笔
when she signed the power of attorney form.
他查明曦地产  看到了佩妮的照片
He looked up Bright Morning Realty, saw Penny's picture.
办公室地址就是房车的位置
That office address was that of the trailer.
你确定他跟这事无关吗
You're sure he's not involved?
我非常特别肯定
I'm pretty freaking positive.
老大  我们第一次跟这家伙谈时他那个样子
Boss, the way that this guy when we first talked to him?
而且我彻查了他的手机
On top of that, I dumped his phone.
跟马斯登夫妇没有联系
There's no connection to the Marsdens.
没有电话  短信
No calls, no texts.
他的出差记录也没问题
His business trip checks out.
我在想  丢掉孩子
I think that, uh, ditching the kid,
是他妻子凯特干的
it's on his wife, Kate.
-给我一分钟  -是  长官
- Give me a minute. - Yes, sir.
听着
Listen.
入室行窃  谋杀未遂
Home invasion, attempted murder,
要坐牢很久的  朋友
is serious time, my friend.
很久
Serious time.
行了
Come on.
你到底为什么跑去见马斯登夫妇
Why'd you really go see the Marsdens?
他们瞒着你什么  还是欠你钱
I mean, they holding out on you? They owe you money?
我觉得我跟那个变态扭曲的世界有关系吗
You think I'm involved in that sick, twisted world?
-我问的是...  -我在说
- I'm asking-- - I'm telling.
我没有
No.
那对夫妻带走了我儿子
That couple took my son.
而且他们把他塞到避雨棚
And they stuck him in a storm shelter.
留他在那里等死
And they left him there to die.
如果是你儿子你会怎么做
What would you do if it was your son?
好的
Okay.
毫无疑问  移民总署刚刚确认了
If there was ever any doubt, just got confirmation from ICE.
没什么克莱德·哈里斯
There is no agent Clyde Harris.
也没有调查父母把收养的孩子
There is no undercover investigation into
送人的卧底行动
parents giving away adopted children.
所以要么是马斯登在说谎
So either the Marsdens are lying,
要么就是扮演克莱德·哈里斯的人
or some monster going by Clyde Harris
把他们耍得团团转
is playing them real hard.
我觉得是后者
I think it's choice number two.
我们知道  有第三个人参与  对吧
I mean, we know there's a third person involved, right?
是的  那个冰毒商人  马歇尔
Yeah, that meth dealer, Marshall?
是的  他说他看到跟小孩子一起的邻居
Yeah, he told us the neighbor he saw with the young kid
是个高高的白人  马斯登挺矮的
was a tall white dude. Marsden is pretty short.
跟关说的也能对上
It matches what Quan said, too.
好  所以克莱德很高  很好
All right, so Clyde's tall. Fantastic.
我们去找他吧
Let's track him down.
不如去I94号的货车停车场吧
Why don't we go to the truck stop at I-94?
看能不能找到什么监控
See if we can pull some video.
我得走了
I gotta go.
乔丹和凡妮莎不接电话
Jordan and Vinessa, they're not answering the phone
-所以...  -好的  好的  我明白
- so-- - Yeah, yeah, I got it.
你快去吧
Go, go, go.
乔丹呢  我打了一天电话都没人接
where's Jordan? I've been calling y'all all day.
好吧  别生我的气
Okay, don't get mad at me.
-我想阻止他  但是  -阻止他干什么
- I tried to stop him, but-- - Stop him from what?
你在说什么  他在这里吗
What are you talking about? Is he here?
他去找那些抓我的男孩了
He went to find the boys who grabbed me.
凡妮莎  你跟我说过你不知道他们是谁
Vinessa, you told me you didn't know who they were.
我撒谎了  我知道其中一个
I lied. I knew one of them.
-迪翁·巴恩斯  -他住在哪里
- Deon Barnes. - Okay, where does he live?
在65街和杰弗森路附近
Near 65 and Jefferson.
乔丹说他要杀了他
Jordan said he was gonna kill him.
什么  你说什么
What? What'd you just say?
他非常生气  我
He was so mad. I--
我操
Damn.
凡妮莎  关上门不要让任何人进来
Vinessa, lock the doors and don't let anybody in this house.
你听到了吗
You hear me?
乔丹  你他妈在干什么
Jordan, what the hell are you doing?
乔丹
Jordan!
乔丹  停
Jordan, stop!
乔丹
Jordan.
Jordan!
-乔丹  -放开我
- Jordan! - Leave me alone, man!
把枪给我  给我
Give me the gun. Give me the gun.
你他妈怎么了  乔丹
What the hell is wrong with you, Jordan?
你要干什么  你要杀了他们
What were you gonna do? You were gonna kill them.
你是要杀了他们吗
You was gonna kill them, huh?
我要是晚来那么一会儿
Well, if I'd have rolled up a minute later,
你早他妈死了
your ass would have been dead.
-我不会  -我知道你不会
- I--I couldn't-- - I know you couldn't.
你知道为什么你不会吗
And you know why you couldn't?
因为你不是那种人  乔丹
Because you're not that person, Jordan.
对吗  那不是你
Okay? That's not you.
妈的  我气疯了  我要打死他
Damn, I'm mad. I get it.
-你也气疯了  -不  你不明白
- You're mad, too. - No, you don't get it.
你什么意思  你以为我不想打死他们吗
What do you mean? You think I don't wanna whoop they ass?
这是你的错
This is your fault.
你让我这么做的  你让我作证
You made me do this. You--You made me testify--
别把锅甩给我  不是这样的
Don't blame it on me, man. It's not like that.
-你为什么要我这么做  -因为我们坐下来
- Why did you make me do it? - Because we sat down
我们决定这是正确的事
and we decided this was the right thing.
是你决定的
You decided!
是你  不是我
You! Not me!
我才不想当什么模范
I don't give a damn about being a role model.
我可不想当
I ain't ask for this.
凡妮莎  她也不想当
Vinessa, she ain't ask for this.
你还不明白吗
Don't you get that?
天啊  乔丹
Damn. Jordan.
乔丹  看着我  兄弟
Jordan, look at me, bro.
我没想到会这样
I didn't mean for that to happen.
我只是尽我所能保护你们
I'm only doing my best to protect y'all.
帮助你们
To be there for y'all.
这次是我错了
I got it wrong this time.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这次确实是我错了  真的
I just got it wrong this time, that's all.
好的  马斯登和关在那里
All right, so there's the Marsdens right there with Quan.
那应该是克莱德·哈里斯
That's gotta be Clyde Harris.
能再放大一点吗
Can you get any closer?
再大就看不清了
Not without sacrificing detail.
有棒球帽反正也看不清
You can't see his face anyway with the ball cap on.
那辆房车上面没有牌照
There's no license plate on that RV.
好像克莱德想要给关一些吃的
Looks like Clyde's trying to give Quan food.
是的  从恩达西汉堡店买的
Yeah, from Burger-N-Dash.
好的  我去调取周围地区的录像
Okay, I'm gonna pull video from nearby locations,
看看有没有能够看清这个人的
see if we can get a better look at this guy.
好的
Right on.
各位
Hey, guys.
有了克莱德·哈里斯的清楚照片
Got a clear image of Clyde Harris
来自于恩达西汉堡店旁边的卡车停车场
from a Burger-N-Dash near the truck stop.
面部识别系统显示是克莱德·杜普里
Facial recognition matches Clyde Dupree.
他有走私象牙的前科
He's got a prior for ivory smuggling.
走私象牙  搞笑吗
Ivory smuggling? Is that a joke?
不是的  他付了1万的罚金
No, uh, he paid a $10,000 fine.
缓刑两个月
He did two months probation.
他的新商业模式也是换汤不换药
His new business model's pretty much the same.
只是换了货物而已
He just changed the cargo.
-给我们一点时间进行包围  -好的
- Give us a sec to get around. - Yeah.
-芝加哥警署  -砸开
- Chicago PD. - Hit it.
他从后门跑了
He went out the back.
停下
Stop!
不许动
Freeze!
-克莱德·杜普里呢  -我不知道那是谁
- Where's Clyde Dupree? - I don't know who that is.
你刚刚就在他的家里
You were just in his apartment.
他今早搬出去了
He moved out this morning.
我想着可以捡一点他剩的东西
I thought I could take what he left behind.
我是在外面乞讨的
I panhandle outside.
我看到他很匆忙收拾东西走了
I saw the guy pack up and leave in a hurry.
他把东西扔进了垃圾箱里
He threw that in the hall dumpster.
我以为我可以捡点破烂卖
I thought I could find something to sell.
副本
银行新业务
避难所拍卖
好像是关于避难所拍卖行的一些资料
Looks like papers for something called Sanctuary Row.
克莱德怎么知道我们在追查他的
How did Clyde know we were on to him?
他很谨慎  会看报纸
He's cautious. Read the papers.
考虑到他三个孩子都死了
Thinks three of his kids are dead.
就知道警察在调查了
Knows the police are all over it.
各位  我找到了关于避难所拍卖行的蛛丝马迹
Guys, I found something. Sanctuary Row.
这个暗网太恶心了
This dark net stuff is pretty rough.
我要洗个澡
I feel like I need a shower.
避难所拍卖行
皇家条纹球蟒  北极狐  黑蝎子
都是外来生物  皇家条纹球蟒
Exotic animals. Royal Stripe Ball Python.
女性  十岁
Female, ten years old.
淡色  懂礼貌  非常少见
Pale coloring, well behaved. Very rare.
他在描述那些孩子
He's talking about the kids.
是的  他列了四种动物
Yeah, he's got four animals listed.
他在贩卖四个孩子
He's selling four kids.
点开这个老链接
Click on this old link.
他已经拍卖了多少个孩子
How many kids has he auctioned off?
-18个  -这个人太变态了
- 18. - This guy's sick.
他建立了一个领养儿童网站来寻找猎物
He sets up a re-homing site so he can find his product,
然后在暗网把他们拍卖掉
and then he auctions them off on the dark net.
上面说还有19分钟拍卖就截止了
Says here the auction closes in 19 minutes.
竞拍成功的人到时候会知道领取孩子的地点
Winners will be notified of a pick-up location at that time.
开始竞拍
Start bidding.
我们怎么付钱
How are we gonna pay for it?
很难短时间筹集这么一大笔钱
It's gonna be tough to get flash money in time.
我来想办法  你们只要负责赢下竞拍就行
Just let me worry about that. You make sure you win.
那笔电子汇款顺利吗
That wire transfer went okay?
顺利  我从你的柜子里拿的钱
Yeah, I took the money from your locker,
让我的线人实际汇的款
had my C.I. make the actual transfer.
-没有指纹  -好的
- Fingerprints aren't on it. - Good.
我今天查了安东尼奥的电话
So, I checked Antonio's phone today.
几天前他接到了伍兹的电话
He got a call a couple nights ago from Woods.
打了3分钟
Lasted three minutes.
-三分钟  -是的
- Three minutes? - Yeah.
所以他们有事要说
So they had something to talk about.
红色接人皮卡进来了
Red pick-up truck coming in.
司机为白人男性  伊利诺伊牌照
White male driver. Illinois tags.
57AV2U
57 Adam Victor 2 Union.
收到  我看到他了
Copy, I see him.
这应该是最后一个了
This should be the last one.
所有竞拍赢家都到了
All the auction winners are here now.
牌照注册人是
All right, plates are registered
玛丽安·瑞奇  松果区788号
to Maryann Richter, 788 Pine Place.
车辆注册信息
玛丽安·瑞奇
这看起来可不像是个叫玛丽安的女人啊
Well, that don't look like a Maryann to me.
白人男性
White, male.
-35岁左右  -好好  稍等
- Mid-30s. - Yeah, yeah, yeah, hold up.
我查到了皮卡的主人的相关信息
I'm getting a, uh, hit on the pick-up's address.
丹尼尔·瑞彻  35岁  注册性侵犯
Daniel Richter, 35, registered sex offender.
跟母亲玛丽安一起住
Lives with his mother, Maryann.
大家都看好手机
All right, check your phones, everybody.
我给你们发这个人的照片
I'm gonna send over a photo of this guy.
我需要确认
I'm gonna need a positive.
亲爱的  我确定今晚要迟到了
Hey, honey. Yeah, I'm positive i'll be late tonight.
确认了  好
That's a positive. Okay.
也爱你
Love you, too.
来了一辆温内巴戈露营车
We've got a Winnebago.
看起来像我们的目标
Yeah, it looks like our guy.
是他  百分百确定
That's him, 100 percent.
-确认  -好  伯吉斯
- Confirmed. - All right, Burgess.
开始慢慢靠近  厄普顿  一样
Start creeping in real slow. Upton, same.
阿特沃特  安东尼奥  听我命令
Atwater, Antonio, on my command.
来
Come on.
快  来
Come on, come on.
需要让他远离那辆房车
We need him away from that trailer.
另外三个孩子有可能也在里面
Chances are the other three kids are in there, too.
行动
Move in.
警察  不许动
Hey, police! Don't move.
不许动
Do not move.
过来
Come on.
退后  否则我杀了她
Back off, or I'll kill her.
求你
Please, please.
-退后  -不要
- Back off! - Please!
不要走了  否则我开枪了
Stop walking, or I'll shoot.
我发誓  我会开枪的
I swear to God, I'll shoot.
我会开枪  我发誓
I'll shoot. I swear to God.
跟我来  没事
Come with me. It's okay.
其他孩子呢
Where are the other kids?
-其他孩子呢  -在露营车里
- Where are the other kids? - In the camper.
其他...
Where are the other--
所有人
All of them.
你都干了半年了
You've been doing this six months.
我不记得
I don't remember.
回答错误
Wrong answer.
你还有最后一次机会  但是这次
You got one last chance. Only this time--
你如果回答错误
You don't give me the right answer...
-行了  -转过身  转过身
- Enough! - Turn over. Turn over!
我要你看着自己死
I want you to see it coming.
汉克  行了
Hank, enough!
警长  杀了他我们就找不到那些孩子了
Hey, Sarge, if you kill him, we can't get the kids.
知道吗
Okay?
汉克
Okay? Hank.
起来  给我起来
Come on, get up. Get up!
起来
Get up!
来吧
Hey, come on, guys.
出来  没事的
Hey, come on out. It's okay.
没事  不要害怕
All right? Don't be scared.
-来  -不要害怕
- Okay? - Don't be scared.
深呼吸  慢慢来
Can you breathe for me? In and out, just slow.
你们安全了
You guy are safe now. All right?
我要律师  我要律师
I want a lawyer. I want a lawyer!
现在
Right now...
是你唯一的机会
Is your one chance to tell me
来告诉我其他孩子在哪里
where the rest of those kids are.
还有给我你所有变态网站的密码
And give me the passwords to all your twisted web sites.
我有什么好处
What's in it for me?
你能活下来
Your ability to live.
什么
Excuse me?
你会去库克县的普通监狱
You're gonna be placed in general population at Cook County.
相信我  我跟你说
And, um, believe me when I tell you...
那里有的是坏人
There's a lot of real bad people there.
但他们有自己的...
But they-They have their own...
行为准则
Code of conduct.
还有
And...
他们唯一都憎恨的
The one thing they really hate...
就是伤害孩子的人
is people who hurt children.
他们会对这种人做各种事
I mean, they do all kinds of things to them.
折磨  强奸
Torture, rape...
你给我我想要的
You give me what I'm asking for...
我就确保你去特殊人群监狱
I'll make sure you're placed in special population.
在那里你会受到保护
You'll be protected there.
否则...
If not, well...
30秒后提议过期
Offer expires in 30 seconds.
你真的会把他放去特殊人群监狱吗
You serious about special population for him?
当然不  我已经给库克县的朋友打过电话了
Hell no. I already called my friend at Cook County.
克莱德会得到应有的惩罚  相信我
Clyde is gonna get what's coming to him, trust me.
巡警找到了克莱德名单上的六个孩子
Patrol picked up six of the kids on Clyde's list.
其他的还没找到
The rest are in the wind.
至少我们救到了一部分
At least we saved some of them, huh?
还好我们及时找到了那个拍卖
It's a good thing we found that auction in time.
对
Yeah.
说到这个
Speaking of which...
你怎么那么快弄到拍卖用的钱的
how'd you get the money for the auction so fast?
你为什么这么感兴趣
Why are you so interested?
好去告诉伍兹吗
So you can tell Woods?
什么
Excuse me?
你一直跟他有联系  不是吗
You've been talking to him, haven't you?
一个叫波特州检察官
Some State's Attorney named Potter.
你监视我
You spied on me?
你这是算承认了吗
That a yes?
波特在查洛佩兹谋杀案
Potter's working the Lopez homicide.
你还记得吧
You remember that, don't you?
-当然  -波特对案子有几个问题
- Oh, yeah. - Potter had a few questions about the case,
因为我们释放洛佩兹后他就死了
since Lopez wound up dead after we released him.
伍兹在场吗
Was Woods there?
在
Yeah.
他们觉得跟我有关
They think I'm involved?
是的
They do.
你怎么说的
What'd you say?
什么都没说
Not a damn thing.
虽然我跟你在一些事上有分歧
You and I might disagree on certain things,
但我不那样做事
but I don't do business like that.
从不
Never have.
兄弟
Hey, man.
好啊  警长
What's up, Sarge?
-来看看  -一切都还好吗
- Checking in. - Yeah, everything okay?
好  谢谢  你呢
Yeah, thanks. How you doing?
我挺好  坐
I'm all right. Take a seat.
谢谢  喝啤酒吗
Thanks. Want a beer?
-不介意来一瓶  -好
- Don't mind if I do. - Yeah.
今天真惊险  是吧
It's been a hell of a day. Right?
敬惊险的一天
To a hell of a day.
嗯
Yeah.
这里真安静  孩子们呢
Quiet around here. Where are the kids?
在去德克萨斯的飞机上
On the plane to Texas.
-德克萨斯  -对  确实是
- Texas? - Yeah, believe it or not.
说到底  警长
I mean, at the end of the day, Sarge,
如果那些孩子真出事  我不会原谅自己
I won't forgive myself if anything really happened to those kids.
所以我做出了最好的决定
So I made the best decision.
为了他们
For them, anyway.
为了我们家
For the family.
嗯
Yeah.
我理解
I understand.